<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Work on Pozibl - the art of the possible</title>
    <link>https://pozibl.com/work/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Work on Pozibl - the art of the possible</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 10:32:45 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://pozibl.com/work/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Data Center Site Selection</title>
      <link>https://pozibl.com/work/data-center-site-selection/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 10:32:45 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>https://pozibl.com/work/data-center-site-selection/</guid>
      <description>Data Center Site Selection (DCSS) is a tool that combines network requirements with geospatial analysis to identify the best location for a new data center. DCSS takes into account factors such as network connectivity, power availability, and environmental risks to help organizations make informed decisions about where to locate their data centers. By using DCSS, organizations ensure that their data centers are located in the optimal location to meet their specific needs.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Large Scale Ftth Feasability</title>
      <link>https://pozibl.com/work/large-scale-ftth-feasability/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 10:32:20 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>https://pozibl.com/work/large-scale-ftth-feasability/</guid>
      <description>When investing in a large scale FTTH project, it is important to conduct a feasibility study to determine the potential return on investment. This involves analyzing the costs and benefits of the project, as well as assessing the market demand and competition.&#xA;Hexvarium developed a unique approach which combine financial modelling, outside plant network design, capital budgeting over time and market analysis to determine the feasibility of a large scale FTTH project.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fiber Location Checker</title>
      <link>https://pozibl.com/work/fiber-location-checker/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 10:31:47 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>https://pozibl.com/work/fiber-location-checker/</guid>
      <description>Often when starting a project it can be hard to determine if there is a real market need for fiber to the home.&#xA;Many factors come into play and often an average take rate percentage is just used.&#xA;This means that the whole business case rests on build it first and they will come!.&#xA;This is a risky approach and can lead to a lot of wasted time and money.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Overture</title>
      <link>https://pozibl.com/work/overture/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 10:31:13 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>https://pozibl.com/work/overture/</guid>
      <description>Customize the public UDF to extract data from Overture Maps.&#xA;Add the option to grab data from a polygon and convert polygons to points.&#xA;Over the past year we have advised on the development of the Fused Platform.&#xA;The Fused Platform is a data platform that allows users to access data from multiple sources and combine it into a single data set. All via using Python code that is already being used by data scientists and analysts.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Regen Ag Shade</title>
      <link>https://pozibl.com/work/regen-ag-shade/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 10:31:00 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>https://pozibl.com/work/regen-ag-shade/</guid>
      <description>Build a new app to use anywhere to determine the shade footprint of a new hedge or solar installation.&#xA;This app will use the Fused API to determine the shade footprint of a new hedge or solar installation. It will be able to determine the amount of shade that will be cast by the new installation and how much sunlight will be blocked. This will help people make informed decisions about where to plant hedges or install solar panels.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA Broadband Data</title>
      <link>https://pozibl.com/work/us-broadband-data/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 10:12:53 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>https://pozibl.com/work/us-broadband-data/</guid>
      <description>Often you want some subset of the data from the FCC BDC map.&#xA;That is a challenge. There is more than 2GB of data as each service location gets a record.&#xA;By downloading the data and grouping it we can make it more useable.&#xA;History There are many versions of this data but this uses the latest &amp;ldquo;*FibertothePremises_fixed_broadband_J23_28nov2023.csv&amp;rdquo;&#xA;https://broadbandmap.fcc.gov/data-download&#xA;There is also data going back further under Form-477.&#xA;Example Data Processing import pandas as pd import glob from shapely.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
