<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Software Tools on Pozibl - the art of the possible</title><link>https://pozibl.com/categories/software-tools/</link><description>Recent content in Software Tools on Pozibl - the art of the possible</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 08:37:17 -0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://pozibl.com/categories/software-tools/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Design Validation</title><link>https://pozibl.com/design-validation/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 08:37:17 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://pozibl.com/design-validation/</guid><description>&lt;p>Are your as-built records fit for your operational needs?&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Pozibl can offer an independent validation of HLD, LLD as well as As-Built designs you receive from 3rd party subcontractors.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Get in touch to see a demonstration of out design validation capability.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>GIS Data Pipelines</title><link>https://pozibl.com/pipelines/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 08:37:17 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://pozibl.com/pipelines/</guid><description>&lt;p>Concerned that you’re not leveraging your GIS assets fully? Using your data effectively can help improve your business decisions, saving you money.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>The AI boom has spawned huge developments in data storage technologies that are optimized for heavy geospatial operations.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>The team at Pozibl have experience implementing end-to-end data pipelines that leverage these latest technologies. Maximise the value embedded in your data by making it accessible throughout the network deployment lifecycle.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Smart Integrations</title><link>https://pozibl.com/integrations/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 08:37:17 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://pozibl.com/integrations/</guid><description>&lt;p>We appreciate that nobody really wants to introduce another software tool or platform to their existing workflow.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Yet existing tools may not have the exact functionality you’re looking for…&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Pozibl offer consulting services to deliver bespoke solutions that address your specific pain points, integrated into your current workflows to ease their adoption.&lt;/p></description></item></channel></rss>